{"data":[{"question":"Did they say they ________ me?","a":"will telephone","b":"would telephone","c":"have telephoned","d":"had telephoned","answer":"2","explain":"- Would: used when you think that someone is willing to do something\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"The ________ of coming in time in small.","a":"possible","b":"possibly","c":"possibility","d":"impossible","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The + noun + of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"There was a nasty ________ at Newton crossroads yesterday morning.","a":"event","b":"accident","c":"happening","d":"emergency","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Accident: a crash involving cars, trains, planes\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"A bus overturned, and some of the passengers were badly ________.","a":"pained","b":"wounded","c":"knocked down","d":"injured","answer":"4","explain":"\u00a0\n- Injured (PII): hurt in an accident\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"Several ________ helped to pull people out of the wreckage.","a":"bystanders","b":"spectators","c":"audience","d":"supporters","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Bystander: someone who watches what is happening without taking part.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"Most of the passengers were found to be suffering from severe ________.","a":"surprise","b":"shock","c":"worry","d":"nervousness","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We often say \"suffering from shock\".","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"The bus had crashed into a brand new car and had completely ________ it, although fortunately there was no one in the car.","a":"hit","b":"knocked","c":"wrecked","d":"crashed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Wreck: to damage something such as a building or vehicle so badly that it cannot be repaired.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"The police took the names and addresses of as many ________ as possible.","a":"suspects","b":"witnesses","c":"viewers","d":"judges","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Witness: someone who sees a crime or an accident and can describe what happened.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"It is believed that the injured passengers have the right to claim ________.","a":"rewards","b":"prizes","c":"refund","d":"compensation","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Compensation: money paid to someone because they have suffered injury or loss, or because something they own has been damaged.\ndemand\/seek\/claim compensation.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"This hat looks ________ on me.","a":"nice","b":"well","c":"beautifully","d":"pretty","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Look\/taste\/smell + Adj.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"}]}